(1) Change all parameters (char, int) to pair<char, int>
(2) Player has a field numChesspieces, which is the number of chesspieces left for a player. Whenever a player's piece is captured, its decreaseNum() is called
(3) Board: add a vector<pair<char, int>>, positions, for each player, which contains all the positions of the player's chesspieces that are left
(4) Board: change the parameter of numPossibleMoves and numPossibleAttacks to an int. Now they can get a number from the player, and use the number to select a position from the vector added in (3)